A Guide to the Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #4836
Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. Papers 1868-1945
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
4836
ca.10,000 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1954 May 7
Container List
- Correspondence
  - Letters (carbons) from Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1915-1916 Sep; (4 folders) (Box Box 1)
  - Letters (carbons) from Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1916 Oct-1924 Aug; (4 folders) (Box Box 2)
  - Letters (carbons) from Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1924 Sep-1925 Mar; (5 folders) (Box Box 3)
  - Letters (carbons) from Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1934-1936; (4 folders) (Box Box 4)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from extended family members, 1901-1937 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his brothers and sisters, 1900-1929 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his daughter, Evelyne Garnett, 1916-1929 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his daughter, Roma Garnett, 1917-1939, n.d. (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his parents, Alfred C. Garnett and Sue Garnett, 1903-1904 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his son, A. Cooke Garnett, 1923-1927 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his son, Frank M. Garnett and his wife, Tina Garnett, 1916-1932 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his son, J. Hugh Garnett, 1919-1939 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his son, Walter R. Garnett and his wife, Ruth Garnett, 1919-1931 (Box Box 5)
  - Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr. from his wife, Nellie Garnett, and related, 1919-1929 (Box Box 5)
  - Personal Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1900-1904; (2 folders) (Box Box 5)
  - Personal Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1913-1938, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 6)
  - Personal Letters to Frank M. Garnett, 1939-1940 (Box Box 6)
  - Religious Letters to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1900-1940, n.d.; (8 folders) (Box Box 6)
- Business and Legal Papers
  - Business Advertisements sent to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., n.d. (Box Box 7)
  - Business Catalogs sent to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1900-1906; (3 folders) (Box Box 7)
  - Business Catalogs sent to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 8)
  - Business Papers of Alfred C. Garnett and Jr.: Promissory Notes, 1868-1903 (Box Box 8)
  - Business Papers of Alfred C. Garnett and Jr., 1876-1902; (3 folders) (Box Box 8)
  - Business Papers of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1903-1918; (6 folders) (Box Box 9)
  - Business Papers of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1919-1939; (6 folders) (Box Box 10)
  - Business Papers of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., n.d. (Box Box 11)
  - Business Papers of Frank M. Garnett, 1939-1941 (Box Box 11)
  - Financial Statements of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1901-1904 (Box Box 11)
  - Legal Papers of Alfred C. Garnett and Jr., 1871-1939, n.d.; (6 folders) (Box Box 11)
- Topical
  - Educational Papers, 1900-1938 (Box Box 12)
  - Federal Government and State Officials, 1901-1928 (Box Box 12)
  - Masonic Lodges, 1898-1921 (Box Box 12)
  - Masonic Lodges: Relief for Family of W. E. Pratt, 1901-1902 (Box Box 12)
  - Medical Papers re Nellie Evelyn Garnett and Nellie Evelyne Garnett, 1928-1934 (Box Box 12)
  - Political Papers, 1902-1932 (Box Box 12)
  - Religious Circulars, 1901-1940; (3 folders) (Box Box 12)
  - Religious Circulars, n.d. (Box Box 13)
- Bound Volumes
  - Check Stubs of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1917-1919; (2 folders--3 volumes) (Box Box 13)
  - Check Book of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1915-1917 (Box Box 13)
  - Day Books of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1897, 1915 (Box Box 13)
  - Inventory Books of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr.'s General Store, 1898-1920 (Box Box 14)
  - List of Checks sent to the Bank by Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1896-1898 (Box Box 14)
  - Mutual Benefit Fire Insurance Association: Minutes of the Buckingham Division, 1895-1897 (Box Box 14)
  - Pamphlets issued by the State of Virginia, 1902-1934 (Box Box 14)
  - Religious: Church Collections, 1915-1932 (Box Box 14)
  - Religious: West Buckingham Methodist Episcopal Church Quarterly Conference Records, 1922-1930; (2 volumes) (Box Box 14)
  - Treasurer's Check Stub Book belonging to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1891-1895 (Box Box 14)
  - Day Book of [Frank M.] Garnett for [General Store], 1944-1945 (Box Oversize)
  - Inventory Books of Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., 1898-1899; (2 volumes) (Box Oversize)
- Oversize
  - Business Advertisements sent to Alfred C. Garnett, Jr., n.d. (Box Oversize)